bizomart.com 2018-12-14

# Bizomart | Privacy

PRIVACY POLICY

The privacy policy is a basic description of the how we collect your "Personal and Professional information", and use it for the smooth functioning of the business. The information supplied by you can be used either for displaying on our Website, or in certain areas that require them. We do not have any vested interest to store your personal information. The main objective of Bizomart.com is to enable you to satisfy your requirements by giving you access to high quality information that can take your business to new heights.

We collect your personal information in order to record, support and facilitate your business enhancement. Along with this, it also enables us to contact you in case there is some information updated on our website that needs your due attention. In order to make our website effective, certain information may be collected each time you visit the website. By using the website, products or services, you give your consent to the collection, utilization and disclosure of your personal Information and professional Information, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

When you visit our Website, certain cookies may be temporarily stored on your system. Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is your choice. If you have not changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the Website. 

Your privacy is our topmost concern

At Bizomart, we make constant and continuous efforts to safeguard your private information to the utmost. We are always committed to protect your privacy, no matter what the situation is. This Privacy Policy governs the way in which we collect your data, and use it further for various purposes. It does not apply to information collected by any other third party (for any official or personal purpose), including any application or content that may be accessible from our website.

By using our products or the Subscription Service, you give your uncompromised consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described here, you should not use our products or the Subscription Service in any regard.

We periodically update our Privacy Policy to serve your needs in the best possible manner. If you subscribe to the Subscription Service, then you will receive notice when this Privacy Policy is modified. However, we clearly state that if you have not subscribed, then it's your sole responsibility to be aware of the changes that we incorporate, or else we will not be expressly or impliedly responsible for any financial or any other loss of property sustained. 

What if you visit our website to read, browse, enhance your knowledge bank or download information?

We appreciate your interest and encourage you to do the same. In this case, Bizomart.com will collect and store the following information: the domain name and host from which you access the Internet; the IP address of the computer you use; the software and the operating system you are using; the date and time of visiting our website; and any other requisite piece of information in this regard.

We also clearly state that Bizomart.Com and related products (BigWigVideos and a host of other products to be launched soon), are property of Bizomart LLC We will be using your personal information to promote the products that are also a part of Bizomart LLC.

But, we clearly would like to assure you that we will not be sharing or using your personal information to provide any monetary benefits to any third party. You can be rest assured that your data is completely safe and secure with us. Through our website, we collect your name, address, email, and telephone number. 

How do we deal with minors?

We duly understand the growing usage of internet amongst the children, and the risks involved with it. So, as our genuine societal concern, we expect and encourage the parents to keep a vigil on the online activities of their children.

So, we make a strong effort not to sell our products or services to children below 18 years. We request you that in case you are a minor, you must not disclose your personal information to us in any circumstances. If we observe that by mistake, we will collect any personal information of children below 18 without parental consent, we will delete that information with minimum delay possible. 

Usage of cookies

Cookies are small files that get transferred to your computer, laptops etc. through a web browser (only if allowed) that enables the sites or service providers to recognize your browser and store and remember useful information.

We use cookies to remember, understand and save your preferences for any future visit and amalgamate data about website traffic so that we can offer better customer experience to you in the near future. No personal information is collected on our website unless that information is knowingly submitted through an opt-in form. It should be duly noted that this information is entered by you only; we don't give any express or implied statement on our website that you have to enter your personal information for any purpose.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or wish to clarify some doubts about any information mentioned here, send us an Email at (please insert ID here) and we will be happy to help. 

Fostering connections with other Websites

While having communication with you (with help of an email), you might receive some advertisements or links to some third- party or parties, who might be directly or indirectly connected with us. We hereby assure you that we don't provide any of your information to these Websites or third parties. We cannot be held liable for any loss or leak of information to these parties.

We are not responsible for any form of transmission received by you from any Linked Website. We also don't make any representations concerning the privacy practices or policies of such third parties or terms of use of such Websites, nor do we control or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, videos, messages, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, or other materials available on such Websites.

Any information, provided by you to any third party, shall be governed as per the rules and regulations applicable to that Website or third party. We do not have any responsibility in such a case. You acknowledge that we are giving these links as a convenience, and cannot be responsible for any mishap that occurs at your end. 

Trademark

The logos, trademark or any other verifiable sign that have been displayed on our website, in our company content or any of our products, are our "Registered" trademarks. We have complete control right on these trademarks, and you are not allowed to make any use of our trademark for any personal or professional purpose, without our prior and written approval. 

Get in touch with us

We are always open and easily accessible for getting in touch with you. Please feel totally free to mail us at [**support@biomart.com**](mailto:support@bizomart.com.). You are also welcome to call us for any queries.
